Employee Engagement û
Highly Engaged
Moderately Engaged
Moderately Disengaged
Highly Disengaged
Remarks: To create 4 such 
liquid 
fill
 gauges
 
each representing the above 4 criteria 
in an animated format
For high achievers, steady performers, needs improvement
Remarks :
  To retain as is
Live Speedometers
Remarks :
  To retain as is
Futuristic radar web
Competency 
List
  -
Business Acumen
Collaboration
Communication
Technology
Execution
Remarks :
  To create a radar 
chart ,
 giving
 a comparison between the ideal requirements for the role (the outer layer) and the employee's current actual scores (the inner layer)
 on the above listed competencies -
Value Chart 
Remarks :
 to retain as is
High performing teams and their leaders
Remarks:
 please give us a better version for the below chart. The below chart is 
highlighting top-performing
 teams with the corresponding managers who have been the pillars is guiding, providing clarity, support system, coaching and guiding the team to raise up to higher level.
Each 
manager
 with a specific numerical metric
 represents the overall team performance scores.
Feedback personas û 
Remarks :
 
The image illustrates "Feedback Personas," 
wherein 
a lenient
 "Liberal 
manager
" 
Vs a
 data-driven "Caring Critic
 manager
."
 
Most
 
of the individual while giving feedback 
lean toward giving pleasing scores to maintain a positive image
. But the true essence of feedback 
is
s
 to move toward
s
 a more judicious, objective approach that uses 
data, 
facts 
based
 feedback to 
enhance 
ones
 growth.
You may want to provide a better 
chart 
version here.
